Register of the Pasternak Family Papers, 1877-2012
Hoover Institution Archives
- PASTERNAK TRUST ARCHIVES, 1877-2012; 118.0 boxes
  - LYDIA PASTERNAK SLATER FILE, 1917-1989; 70.0 boxes
    - Correspondence, 1918-1989 (Box 63-110)
      - General, 1918-1989 and undated (Box 65-110)
        - Bojese, Sigurd Bo, 1972
        - Bolme-Krongsgarten, Elisabeth, 1945
        - Bonchuer, Elisabeth, 1983
        - Book Week, 1964-1966
        - Bookbinder, Svetlana, 1981
        - Books, undated
        - Bookseller, 1960
        - Boothey, Beryl, 1980
        - Borinski, Margaret, 1973-1979 and undated
        - Born, Anne, 1976-1984 (Box-folder 73: 2)
        - Bose, A., 1964-1968
        - Boston Globe, 1961
        - Botteghe Oscure, 1959
        - Bowde, Guy, 1962-1963
        - Bowker Company, 1959
        - Bowra, Maurice, 1958, 1968
        - Bower, Richard, 1975
        - Bouring, Giles, 1972
        - Bowsher, Rodney, 1975
        - Box, Lionel W., 1970
        - Bradbrook, Frank, 1965
        - Bradbury, Robert, 1968
        - Bradburg, R., 1967
        - Bradshaw, Hillary, 1972-1979 and undated (Box-folder 73: 3)
        - Bradshaw, Jennifer, 1977
        - Braig, Alec, 1964
        - Brailowsky, Iurii, 1936
        - Brandeis University, 1964-1965
        - Bratburg, Robert, 1968
        - Braukman, Reiner, 1980
        - Breitman, Michael, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 73: 4)
        - Bressey, Chris, 1966
        - Bressey, Nancy, 1961-1988 and undated
        - Brewster, Stella, 1972-1974
        - Brighton Public Libraries, 1962
        - Brina, Micheline, 1968-1969
        - Brinson, Gunn, 1983
        - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1958-1987 and undated (Box-folder 73: 5)
        - British Council, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 73: 6)
        - British-Italian Society, 1966
        - British Medical Association, 1955
        - British Museum, 1945-1977
        - British United Provident Association, 1967, 1973
        - Brodäer(?), 1966
        - Brodskii, Iosif, 1968-1971
        - Brooks, Meryl, 1974
        - Brown, Alec, 1959
        - Brown, Best and Co. Ltd., 1972
        - Brown, Elsie, 1984
        - Brown, Gunilla, 1970-1974
        - Bruce, L., 1965
        - Brück, Eva and Joseph, 1960 and undated (Box-folder 73: 7)
        - Bruk, N., 1960
        - Bryer, Betty, 1968-1974 and undated
        - Buchanan, George, 1969-1972
        - Buchanan, H. G., undated
        - Buckman, David, 1974
        - Bulgakov, Valerii, 1965
        - Bülow, 1954-1981 (Box-folder 73: 8)
        - Bundesversicherunganstalt für Angestellte, 1968
        - Burall, A. A., 1963
        - Burden-Muller, Rowland, 1960
        - Burdianskii, S., 1961-1966
        - Burgess, Anthony, 1966
        - Buri, S. G., 1967
        - Burnbury, 1946
        - Burndy Library, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 73: 9)
        - Burns, Gilbert, 1967-1968
        - Butcher, Margaret, 1964
        - Buttberg, Moure, undated
        - Butterfield, Penelope, 1967
        - Butterworth, Olga, 1960-1975
        - Buyan, Adil, 1976
        - Caan, Piet, 1985 (Box-folder 74: 1)
        - Cadoux, Aldyth, 1968-1974 and undated
        - Cadoux, Thea, 1968-1979
        - Caedmon Records, Inc., 1966-1968
        - Calasso, Melisenda, 1967
        - Calizi, Jean, 1963 (Box-folder 74: 2)
        - Callander, Elsie, 1968
        - Cambridge University Jewish Society, 1961
        - Cameron, Bella, 1976-1977
        - Campbell, Edna, 1963
        - Canada Council, 1969
        - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1980-1986
        - Canteras(?), William, 1943
        - Cappelini, Mary, 1966-1984 (Box-folder 74: 3)
        - Caprio, Gerald, 1968
        - Carcanet Press, 1970-1971
        - Carey, Renata, 1988
        - Cargills Ltd, 1973
        - Carpenter, Maurice, 1972-1973
        - Carter, Anne, 1973-1980
        - Carstairs, Charlotte, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 74: 4)
        - Casalini libri, 1973
        - Casimir, Hazel, 1963-1964
        - Casimir, Paul (see also Unicorn), 1961-1962 and undated
        - Centre Psychiatrique du Rouvray, 1978
        - Central Office of Information, 1981-1982
        - Chamber(?), Mary, 1961
        - Chapman, Robin, 1942, 1945
        - Chappell, Richard, 1984, 1986
        - Charity, Judith, 1976 (Box-folder 74: 5)
        - Charkerdschi, N., undated
        - Chatto and Windus Ltd., 1967-1972
        - Chelsea Art Club, undated
        - Cheltenham Festival of Literature, 1962
        - Chernosvitova, Evgeniia, 1970
        - Christian, R. F., 1965, 1968
        - Christian, Rosalind, 1968
        - Christian Science Monitor, 1970
        - Christolhas(?), A., 1987
        - Chukovskiĭ, Korneĭ, 1962-1964
        - Churchill, Clementine (see also: National Committee for Rescue from Nazi Terror), 1942-1943
        - Churchill College, Cambridge, 1966, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 74: 6)
        - Chuti, Pra Chakarindh, 1976
        - Cinbalova, Anastasiia, 1967-1969
        - City Art Gallery, Bristol, 1958-1967
        - City Art Gallery, Sheffield, 1978, 1980
        - City Museum and Art Gallery, Burmingham, 1958
        - Clarendon Press, 1972-1973
        - Claris, Wendy, 1970
        - Clark, Charles Jordan, undated
        - Clark, Kenneth, 1962
        - Clarke and Satchell Ltd., 1962
        - Classics Club, 1959-1963
        - Clayre, Alasdair, undated
        - Clough, Francis, 1960-1971 and undated (Box-folder 74: 7-9)
          - 1960-1961 (Box-folder 74: 7)
          - 1962-1963 (Box-folder 74: 8)
          - 1964-1971 and undated (Box-folder 74: 9)
        - Clouts, Sydney, 1979 (Box-folder 75: 1)
        - Colacieli, Flavia, 1946, 1955-1987
        - Colacieli, Piero, 1959-1960
        - Collard, D., 1969
        - Cole and Cole, 1965-1969
        - Collet’s Holdings Ltd., 1975 (Box-folder 75: 2)
        - Collieu, Alison, 1972, 1986
        - Collins Pubishers, 1957-1960
        - Common Ground (951) Ltd., 1962
        - Communication and Marketing Partnership, Ltd., 1984
        - Conaghan, Hannah, 1986
        - Constable Publishers, London, 1967
        - Constairs, Charles, 1976-1978, 1982
        - Constantine Air Freight Services Ltd, 1972
        - Contemporary Poetry and Music Circle, 1960-1966
        - Cooke, Nicholas, undated
        - Cooke, S. M., 1973
        - Cookson, William, 1962
        - Cooling Galleries (London) Ltd., 1957
        - Cooper, Gerda, 1983, 1985
        - Cork, Martha, 1982
        - Corriere della Sera, 1963
        - Coter, Esther, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 75: 3)
        - Cowell, Adrian, 1978
        - Cox, Oliver, 1966-1975
        - Craig, A., 1964
        - Craine, Marjorie, 1983
        - Craine Kalman Gallery, 1973
        - Cresset Press, 1964
        - Cripps, Sheila, 1981
        - Cross, Venetia, 1975 and undated
        - Crossman, Shirley, 1967
        - Crawley and de Reya, 1959
        - Dahl, Jelena, 1979 (Box-folder 75: 4)
        - Dahl, Marianne, 1969-1988
        - Dailis, Genrietta (Eta), 1967 and undated (Box-folder 75: 5)
        - Daily Mail, London, 1959
        - Daily Sketch, 1961
        - Daily Telegraph, 1966, 1968
        - Daily Worker, 1966
        - Dalmati, Margarita, 1963-1970
        - Damme, R., 1925
        - Danavox, 1980
        - Dannfelt, Julian, 1935, 1960-1965
        - Darby and Son, 1965 (Box-folder 75: 6)
        - Darton, Longman and Todd, Ltd., 1964
        - Dartsford, H., 1974
        - Das, Prafula Chandra, 1961-1962
        - Dasgupta, Gayatri, 1968
        - Dave, Mukund, 1973-1975
        - Davey, Andrew, undated
        - Davey, Helen, 1964
        - David Higham Associates, Ltd., 1963
        - Davidson, Magnus, 1942
        - Davies, Anna, 1972
        - Davies, H. R., 1970
        - Davies, Jessie, 1975-1986 and undated (Box-folder 75: 7)
        - Davies, John, undated (Box-folder 75: 8)
        - Davies, Richard, 1977-1987
        - Davies, Rhys, 1970
        - Davies, Robin, undated
        - Dawes, Winifred, 1962-1987 (Box-folder 75: 9)
        - Dayton, Irene, 1972-1988 (Box-folder 75: 10-11)
          - 1972-1981 (Box-folder 75: 10)
          - 1982-1988 (Box-folder 75: 11)
        - Dean, Michel (Mike), 1971-1976 and undated (Box-folder 76: 1)
        - Decreus, Juliette and Eric, 1969-1979
        - Demskaia, Aleksandra, 1973-1980 and undated
        - Denisova, Aleksandra, 1976
        - Denman College, 1968
        - Deugd, C. de, 1967
        - Deutsch, Babette, 1958-1966 (Box-folder 76: 2)
        - Devon, Virginia, 1970
        - Dewhurst, Martin, 1962-1965
        - Dialogue, undated
        - Dickenson, Donna, undated
        - Dijur, Ilja, 1963
        - Disc, Imogen, 1966
        - Dische, Irene, 1988
        - Discurio, 1960
        - Di Simplicio, Dagmar, 1977
        - Di Simplicio, Oscar, 1977
        - Divorce Registry (United Kingdom), 1954
        - Dixon, Heather, 1970 (Box-folder 76: 3)
        - Dobrushina, Vera, 1971 and undated
        - Dobrovein, Maria, 1960, 1965
        - Dobson, Jeremy, undated
        - D’Offey, Anthony, 1973
        - Doljansky, Vera, 1970-1975
        - Döring, Johanna Renata, 1962
        - Dorman, Nina, undated
        - Douglas, Rosemary, 1971
        - Dragon School, Oxford, 1951
        - Druckerel Kempkes Offset+ Buchdruck GmbH, 1971
        - Druckzache, 1965
        - Drule, Irene, 1966
        - DU-Verlag, 1975 (Box-folder 76: 4)
        - Dudak, Nina, 1968
        - Dukas, Helen, 1959-1971
        - Duckle, Richard, 1961
        - Dunn, R., 1970
        - Dunton, Christopher, 1979 and undated
        - Durben, Maria-Magdalena, 1974-1986
        - Durben, Wolfgang, 1983
        - Durrant’s Press Cuttings Ltd., 1966-1969
        - Dyck, J. W., 1967, 1970
        - Dyson, H. V. D., 1967
        - E. S. Frith Windrush Studio, 1962 (Box-folder 76: 5)
        - Eackonski, Karen, 1985
        - Economist, 1982
        - Edinburgh University Library, 1981
        - Éditions du Seuil, 1963-1973
        - Editions Gallimard, 1961
        - Editions Seghers, 1970
        - Edwards, Irene, 1966
        - Eggarter, Charlotte, 1945
        - Egiz, Elena, 1974, 1986 and undated
        - Ehrlich, Moses, L., 1962
        - Einstein, Margot, 1958-1975 (Box-folder 76: 6-7)
          - 1958-1962 (Box-folder 76: 6)
          - 1963-1975 (Box-folder 76: 7)
        - Eisenberg, L., 1927 (Box-folder 76: 8)
        - Ekins, K. M., 1970
        - Elck, P., 1961
        - Elek Books, Ltd., 1958-1962
        - Ellis, Frank, undated
        - Ellis, R. E., 1971
        - Eluaschvili, Jakov, 1972
        - Enaceanu, Marius, 1968, 1972 (Box-folder 76: 9)
        - Encounter, 1957-1970 and undated
        - Encyclopaedia Judaica, 1968-1985
        - Engel (?)., Ada, 1968
        - Engelhardt, W. A., 1958, 1965
        - English, David, 1971-1972
        - Ensby, Michael, undated
        - EP Group of Companies, 1975, 1977
        - Erak, G., 1974 (Box-folder 77: 1)
        - Ermler, Dina and Mark, 1986
        - Ernest Benn Ltd., 1965
        - Ernst, Konrad, 1982-1987
        - Erteschik, Arno, 1946
        - Esterer, Marie Louise, 1961, 1970-1973
        - Ettinger, Pavel, 1939, 1947-1948
        - Expressen, Stockholm, 1972
        - Europa news magazine, 1970
        - F. Biscoe-Taylor and Son, 1975 (Box-folder 77: 2)
        - F. Hoffmann-La Roche and Co. AG, 1934
        - F. M. Blackwell, 1973-1974
        - Fadejev, Anatol, 1961-1962
        - Fajans, Kazimir, 1967-1975
        - Fajans, L., 1963-1976
        - Farmer, Margie, 1966
        - Fawan, James, undated
        - Federation of Jewish Relief Organizations, 1967-1981
        - Fedorow, Tatiana, 1963-1964 and undated (Box-folder 77: 3)
        - Feigen, Josephine, 1960-1961
        - Feldman, Lew D., 1976
        - Fell, Anthony, 1966
        - Ferber, Albert, 1973-1974
        - Fenton Oxford Press, 1961-1962
        - Ferret, Mabel, 1978-1979
        - Feyer, Ingeborg, 1963
        - Figaro, 1960-1961
        - Financial Times, 1987
        - Fine Art Gallery, 1967
        - Finlow, Kathleen, 1953-1976 and undated (Box-folder 77: 4-5)
          - 1953-1966 (Box-folder 77: 4)
          - 1967-1976 and undated (Box-folder 77: 5)
        - Finlow, Simon, 1974 (Box-folder 77: 6)
        - Fise, Boris, 1969, 1984
        - Fisher, Markoosha, 1960
        - Fisher, Mary, 1982
        - Fisher, Patty, 1969
        - Fisher-Reitböck, Ilse, 1982
        - Fishloch, Manon, 1974, 1976
        - Fisler, Jean, 1967
        - Fitzwilliam Museum, Cambridge, 1972
        - Fjeldseth, Eva, 1981
        - Flak, Gizela, 1972
        - Flegon Press, 1965
        - Fleishman, Lazar, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 77: 7-8)
          - 1975-1979 (Box-folder 77: 7)
          - 1981-1986 and undated (Box-folder 77: 8)
        - Fluss, S. S., 1961 (Box-folder 77: 9)
        - Ford, Stephen, 1966
        - Foreign Office, 1947
        - Fouquet, undated
        - France. Ambassade (Germany), 1937
        - France, Anna Kay, 1973-1979
        - France, Peter, 1974
        - Frank R. Newens, 1958
        - Franklin Library, 1982-1983
        - Franklin, Michael, 1969
        - Fraser, Olive, 1961-1977 (Box-folder 77: 10)
        - Franz, Mathys, 1975 (Box-folder 78: 1)
        - Freadman, Richard, 1984 (Box-folder 78: 1)
        - Freeman, Doreen, 1962-1963, 1972
        - Freiberger-Sheikholeslami, Erika, 1971, 1974
        - French, Tina, 1961
        - Friedman, Victor, 1980-1989 and undated
        - Friends of the Art Museum of Israel, 1958, 1971-1972
        - Friends of the Ashmolean, 1985
        - Frisby, P. M., 1966
        - Frolova, Kapitolina, 1960-1976 (Box-folder 78: 2)
        - Frontier, 1958, 1965-1966
        - Fudge and Co. Ltd., 1964-1979 (Box-folder 78: 3)
        - Gabrichevsky (Gabritschevsky) family, 1932-1977 and undated (Box-folder 78: 4-5)
          - 1932-1965 (Box-folder 78: 4)
          - 1966-1977 and undated (Box-folder 78: 5)
        - Gaigalas (Salys), Rima (Rimgaila), 1975, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 78: 6)
        - Galatia, John, 1975
        - Galerie Britscher, 1962
        - Galerie St. Etienne, 1959
        - Gallery Bookstore, 1961
        - Gammann, Karin, 1961-1962
        - Gan, Pavel, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 78: 7)
        - Gardner, Derek, 1955, 1960
        - Garnier, Pierre, 1970
        - Gass, Boris, 1986
        - Gatniejewski, Alwis, 1980
        - Gatova, Larisa, 1959, 1974
        - Gaye, Bertl, 1962-1969
        - Geiringer, Mathilde, 1967, 1970
        - Geldart, Jacqueline, 1963
        - Gendlin, Leonard, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 78: 8)
        - General Welfare of the Blind, 1966
        - Gent, Nicholas, 1971, 1973
        - George Allen and Unwin Ltd., 1961-1986 and undated (Box-folder 78: 9-11; 79: 1-2)
          - 1961-1962 (Box-folder 78: 9)
          - 1963-1964 (Box-folder 78: 10)
          - 1965-1969 (Box-folder 78: 11)
          - 1970-1974 (Box-folder 79: 1)
          - 1975-1986 and undated (Box-folder 79: 2)
        - George Cohn, 1957-1975 (Box-folder 79: 3-5)
          - 1957-1964 (Box-folder 79: 3)
          - 1967-1970 (Box-folder 79: 4)
          - 1971-1975 (Box-folder 79: 5)
        - George, H., 1974 (Box-folder 79: 6)
        - George, Jennifer, 1962
        - George Rainbird, Ltd., 1963-1964
        - Germany, Botschaft (United Kingdom), 1967
        - Gersdorf, Gunther, 1962
        - Ghose, Amal, 1979-1980
        - Giangiacomo Feltrinelli Editore, 1958-1965
        - Gibb, Timothy, 1974
        - Gibson, Dorothy, 1960-1988 and undated (Box-folder 79: 7-8)
          - 1960-1968 (Box-folder 79: 7)
          - 1970-1988 and undated (Box-folder 79: 8)
        - Gibson, Douglas, 1952-1983 and undated (Box-folder 79: 9)
        - Gibson, Dorothy and Douglas, 1961-1985 and undated (Box-folder 79: 10)
        - Gibson and Weldon, 1969 (Box-folder 80: 1)
        - Gifford, Henry, 1977-1989
        - Gildesgame, Pierre, 1973
        - Gilerson, Boris, 1982
        - Glan, Antony, 1961
        - Glass, Adele, 1981
        - Goad, Michael, 1970
        - Godbert, Geoffrey, 1987
        - Goddard, A. J., 1977
        - Godzjaszwiei, L., 1975
        - Gofts, Helen, undated
        - Gold, Edward, 1961
        - Goldberg, Anatol, 1967
        - Goldenberg, Anne Marie, 1953-1988 and undated (Box-folder 80: 2-5)
          - 1953-1969 (Box-folder 80: 2)
          - 1970-1981 (Box-folder 80: 3)
          - 1982-1984 (Box-folder 80: 4)
          - 1985-1988 (Box-folder 80: 5)
        - Goldenberg, Theo, 1968-1982 and undated (Box-folder 80: 6)
        - Goldfarb, Ellen, 1960 (Box-folder 80: 7)
        - Goldhaber, Gertrude, 1964-1974
        - Goldovskaia, Tatiana, 1965
        - Goldscheilder, Fritz, 1928
        - Gömöri, George, 1967
        - Gonnelli, Paolo, 1965
        - Gordon, Dino, 1981
        - Gore-Booth, Angus, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 80: 8)
        - Gore-Booth family, 1959-1974 (Box-folder 80: 9)
        - Görlach, Manfred, 1968 (Box-folder 80: 10)
        - Gorovitch, Michael, 1960-1962
        - Gorringes of Victoria, 1966
        - Gorton, P., 1972
        - Gosudarstvennyi muzei L. N. Tolstogo, 1959
        - Gosudarstvennyi Russkii muzei (letter copied by Lydia Pasternak), 1965
        - Göttling, Trudi, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 80: 11)
        - Goul, Roman, 1962-1965
        - Gough, Malcolm, 1976-1983
        - Gracie, Alan, 1966
        - Grafe, Lukas (L. F. Grafe), 1968-1975
        - Graphikum, 1962-1983 (Box-folder 80: 12; 81: 1-4)
          - 1962-1967 (Box-folder 80: 12)
          - 1968-1971 (Box-folder 81: 1)
          - 1972-1977 (Box-folder 81: 2)
          - 1978-1980 (Box-folder 81: 3)
          - 1981-1983 (Box-folder 81: 4)
        - Greater London Arts Association, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 81: 5)
        - Great Britain – USSR Association, 1967-1988
        - Greene, James, 1975
        - Greenway, Cornelius, 1961
        - Gregory, Robin (see also: Orbis and HUB Publications Ltd.), 1971-1981 and undated (Box-folder 81: 6)
        - Grenel, Annelize, 1982, 1986 (Box-folder 81: 7)
        - Grey, Peter, 1961
        - Greville Press, 1979
        - Griffith, George, 1976
        - Grinberg, R., 1959-1960
        - Grindea, Miron, 1959-1961
        - Grobble, Beatrice, 1981, 1985
        - Groll, Sara, 1966
        - Grüning, Michael, 1983-1988 and undated (Box-folder 81: 8)
        - Guardian, 1960-1987 and undated (Box-folder 81: 9)
        - Güeli, Eola, 1967
        - Gulman, Ray, 1969
        - Gummel, Joan, 1958
        - Gunn, Dairmid, 1981-1986
        - Guptara, Parbhu S., 1980
        - Gurdus, Luba K., 1981
        - Hadfield, Patrick, 1980 (Box-folder 81: 10)
        - Haggs, E., 1966
        - Haig, Alec, 1962
        - Haight, Amanda, undated
        - Haissinsky, J., 1976
        - Haïssinsky, M., 1975-1976
        - Hailsick, Manetta, 1965
        - Haitzman, Silvia, 1986
        - Halinbourg, Beryl, 1975-1987 and undated (Box-folder 81: 11-12)
          - 1975-1980 (Box-folder 81: 11)
          - 1981-1987 and undated (Box-folder 81: 12)
        - Hall, Martin, 1960 and undated (Box-folder 82: 1)
        - Hall, Peter, 1976
        - Hall, Peter, undated
        - Hall, Robert, 1960
        - Hall, S., 1980-1985 and undated
        - Hallie, B., 1959
        - Hammarskjõld, Ellen, 1974
        - Hammer, Ardyn R., undated
        - Hanf, James, 1977-1981
        - Hanisson, Hilda, 1963
        - Harari, Michael, 1970
        - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc., 1976
        - Hardy, Sophia, 1972
        - Hare Duke, Priscilla, 1972
        - Hare, Richard, 1961
        - Harkevitch, Nina, 1932-1987 (Box-folder 82: 2-8)
          Includes a letter from A. Harkevitch, with three letters from Nina Kharkevitch to her, 1932.
          - 1932-1937 (Box-folder 82: 2)
          - 1946-1963 (Box-folder 82: 3)
          - 1964-1965 (Box-folder 82: 4)
          - 1966-1967 (Box-folder 82: 5)
          - 1968-1969, 1960s (Box-folder 82: 6)
          - 1970-1976 (Box-folder 82: 7)
          - 1981-1987 and undated (Box-folder 82: 8)
        - Harris, Agnes, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 82: 9)
        - Harris, John, 1961-1964, 1979
        - Harvey, Norman, 1963-1964
        - Harvill Press Ltd., 1959
        - Haskell, Lara and Vera, 1975
        - Hauser, Olga, 1968-1977 (Box-folder 82: 10)
        - Hay, Peter, 1967
        - Haynes, Alan, 1980 and undated
        - Hayward, Max and Sheila, 1963-1978
        - Hebrew University of Jerusalem, 1985 (Box-folder 83: 1)
        - Hegarty, W. J., 1960
        - Helen and Kurt Wolf Books (see also: Helen Wolf and Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc.), 1973
        - Hellmer, Kurt, 1960
        - Helvetica Press Inc., 1972-1973
        - Hemp, Marjory, 1973
        - Hemphreys, Adam, 1966
        - Henderson, David Rowan, 1966
        - Henley, Sylvia, undated
        - Henry, Bill, 1968
        - Henry, Juliette, 1968
        - Henry, Peter, 1959-1986
        - Herald, Dorothy, 1978
        - Herald Tribune, New York, 1964-1966
        - Herbert Art Gallery and Museum, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 83: 2)
        - Hermann-Gmeiner-Fond Deutschland e.V., undated
        - Herman, Nini, 1967-1972
        - Hesse, Ninon, 1962 (Box-folder 83: 3)
        - Heywood, S., 1963
        - Hicks, Susan, 1976
        - Higginbotham, Jay, 1986
        - Higgs, Jean, 1961
        - Hills, D., 1980
        - Hind, A. M., 1944-1945
        - Hind, Dorothy, 1958, 1964
        - Hindell, Juliet, 1981 and undated
        - Hind-O’Malley, Pamela, 1966-1976 and undated
        - Hingley, Ronald, 1982
        - Hirsh, John, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 83: 4)
        - Hirsh, John, 1967
        - Historia Photo, Kulturgeschitliches Bildarchiv, 1965
        - Hoch, Max, 1973-1979
        - Hoffmann (Schirach), Henrietta, 1961-1965 and undated (Box-folder 83: 5)
        - Hofmannsthal, 1965 (Box-folder 83: 6)
        - Hogg, David, 1968
        - Hogg, Quentin, 1943
        - Holdan Books, Ltd., 1974-1981
        - Holdsworth, Brian, 1959, 1972
        - Hollandia n.v., 1959
        - Holman, Irina, 1983 (Box-folder 83: 7)
        - Holman, Michael (see also: University of Leeds), 1962, 1973-1976
        - Holmes, Frank, 1981
        - Holloway, J., 1964-1965
        - Holton, Jane
        - Homerton College, Cambridge, 1969
        - Honey-Taylor, Alison and Simon, 1988
        - Honig, Camille R. (see also: I and Thou), 1967-1970. (Box-folder 83: 8)
        - Honig, Patricia, undated (Box-folder 83: 9)
        - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace, 1986 (Box-folder 83: 10)
        - Hõrl, Ernst, 1972
        - Hornstein, Yakov (Iania), 1961-1983
        - Horser, S. W., 1968
        - Horwell, A., 1958
        - Hossiason, Olga and Philippe, 1945-1974 (Box-folder 83: 11)
        - Hossiason, Philippe, 1945-1977 and undated (Box-folder 83: 12)
        - Howard, F. (?), 1958 (Box-folder 84: 1)
        - Howard, Stephen, 1969
        - Hraikevitch(?), 1958
        - Hub Publications (see also: ORBIS and Gregory, Robin), 1973-1976 and undated
        - Hubbard, J., 1972
        - Huckin, Mary, 1969
        - Hudson Review, 1963-1965
        - Hughes, Olga, circa 1970
        - Hughes, W. G., 1984
        - Humphries, Adan, 1966 (Box-folder 84: 2)
        - Hunter, David, 1971
        - Hutcheon, Arthur and Jean, 1959
        - Hutchins, Paul and Keri, 1969-1981 and undated
        - Hüttenback, Marie and Milly, 1961-1972
        - 1969-1970 (Box-folder 84: 3)
        - Iamaikina-Ioel’son, Sofia, 1965
        - Ifan, Kyrle Fletcher, 1961
        - Il Giornio, 1961
        - Iljinsky, Natalia, 1964
        - Iljinsky, Paul and Natalia, 1974
        - Illustration Research Service, 1967
        - Ilyinsky, Oleg, 1967
        - Imbert, Olga, 1972
        - Industrial Photo Equipment Ltd., 1958-1959
        - Innis, Pauline, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 84: 4)
        - Innis, Walter, 1974
        - Insel Verlag, Frankfurt am Main, 1983
        - Institut Nėerlandais, 1969
        - Institute of Contemporary Art (ICA), 1961
        - Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes, 1968